A Register of the Juan Lechin Oquendo Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Photographs, 1928-2000. (Box 20)
  - Juan Lechín Oquendo
    - Two prints depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo with his daughter-in-law and granddaughter, 1987 (Folder 20: 38)
    - Three prints depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo at a meeting in support of the Palestine Liberation Organization, Cochabamba, Bolivia, 1988 April 23-25 (Folder 20: 39)
    - One print depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo and Julia Urquidi, circa 1990 (Folder 20: 40)
    - One print depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo and Liber Forti, circa 1990 (Folder 20: 41)
    - Two prints depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo, circa 1990 (Folder 20: 42)
    - Four prints depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo at a reception in the Peruvian embassy, La Paz, Bolivia, 1992 (Folder 20: 43)
    - Three prints depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo, circa 1994 (Folder 20: 44)
    - Four prints depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo, circa 1995 (Folder 20: 45)
    - Three prints depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo, 1996 (Folder 20: 46)
    - Five prints depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo at an exposition of photographs of Bolivian miners, Museo naconal de Arte, La Paz, Bolivia, 1998 September (Folder 20: 47)
    - Five prints depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo, circa 2000 (Folder 20: 48)
    - Two prints depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo, 2000 (Folder 20: 49)
  - Others
    - Six prints depicting Bolivian mines and mineworkers, undated (Folder 20: 50)
    - Seven prints depicting scenes of protest in Bolivia, undated (Folder 20: 51)
    - One print depicting an assembly of Bolivian mineworkers, circa 1952 (Folder 20: 52)
    - One print depicting a May Day march in La Paz, Bolivia, 1978 May 1 (Folder 20: 53)
    - One print depicting a scene of a coup d'état, La Paz, Bolivia, 1979 (Folder 20: 54)
    - One print depicting a demonstration by Bolivian mineworkers, circa 1983 (Folder 20: 55)
    - One print depicting a political rally in Bolivia, 1983 (Folder 20: 56)
    - Two prints depicting workers on a hunger strike, La Paz, Bolivia, 1984 (Folder 20: 57)
    - One print depicting an assembly of mineworkers, La Paz, Bolivia, 1984 (Folder 20: 58)
    - One print depicting a meeting of mineworkers, Milluni, Bolivia, 1985 (Folder 20: 59)
    - Two prints depicting scenes of a state of siege, La Paz, Bolivia, 1985 (Folder 20: 60)
    - One print depicting Bolivian mineworkers on a hunger strike, 1985 October 2 (Folder 20: 61)
- Sound Recordings, 1987-1997. (Box 21)
  Compact sound cassettes, largely containing interviews with Juan Lechín Oquendo
  - Fifteen compact sound cassettes containing a series of autobiographical interviews with Juan Lechín Oquendo, undated (Folder 21: 1-15)
  - Ten compact sound cassettes containing interviews with Juan Lechín Oquendo, 1987 May-September (Folder 21: 16-25)
  - Three compact sound cassettes relating to a trial involving Felipe Quispe Huanca, 1992 (Folder 21: 26-28)
  - Seventeen compact sound cassettes containing a series of autobiographical interviews with Juan Lechín Oquenco, 1997 September-November (Folder 21: 29-45)
- Oversize Materials, 2000-2001. (Box 22)
  Posters, resolution, ceremonial sash, diploma, and serial issues, arranged chronologically
  - Two posters depicting Juan Lechín Oquendo, circa 2000 (Folder 22: 1-2)
  - Official resolution conferring the Orden Nacional del Cóndor de los Andes upon Juan Lechín Oquendo, 2000 April 24 (Folder 22: 3)
  - One ceremonial sash associated with the awarding of the Orden Nacional del Cóndor de los Andes to Juan Lechín Oquendo, 2000 May 4 (Folder 22: 4)
  - One diploma associated with the awarding of the Orden Nacional del Cóndor de los Andes to Juan Lechín Oquendo, 2000 May 4 (Folder 22: 5)
  - One serial issue with an article about the awarding of the Orden Nacional del Cóndor de los Andes to Juan Lechín Oquendo, 2000 May 7 (Folder 22: 6)
  - Three serial issues containing articles concerning the death of Juan Lechín Oquendo, 2001 August 28-29 (Folder 22: 7-9)